Natalie Wischkowski

Curriculum Vitae



PROFILE

I am passionate about fashion, interested in different cultures and strive to overcome challenges. Based on my experience as a former competitive athlete in fencing, self-reliance, endurance and discipline are main principals in my every-day life.

CONTACT

Address

Corso San Gottardo 1, 20136 Milano

Telephone

+491703239259

Fmail

nataliewischkowski@web.de

Linkedin

anatalie-wisckkowski

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sept 2017 - Jan 2018

Student Assistant

FHWS - University for Applied Science Würzburg - Germany

International Office Department

- Organisation, planning and coordination of events.
- Conception of communication strategies and channels.

Mar 2017 - Oct 2017

Trainee

Mekra Lang Group Ergersheim - Germany

Sales management OEM parts

- Creation of parts series planning
- Conception and communication of product offerings for potential customers.
- Customer service
- Order processing

Apr 2016 - Oct 2016

Trainee

Mercedes Benz (Daimler AG) Stuttgart - Germany

International sales department

- Creation of market and dealer spread analyzes
- Creation and preparation of KPI analyzes
- Preparation of presentation and aims of the after sales and sales manager
- Preparation of sales reports
- Support in operational planning

Oct 2015 - Apr 2016

Internship

Mercedes Benz (Daimler AG) Stuttgart - Germany

International after sales management, customer service & parts

- Design and preparation of regular market meetings
- Monitoring of Market performance
- Preparation of committee proposals
- Support in operational planning
- Preparation of presentation and aims of the after sales & sales manager

Natalie Wischkowski

Curriculum Vitae



PROFILE

I am passionate about fashion, interested in different cultures and strive to overcome challenges. Based on my experience as a former competitive athlete in fencing, self-reliance, endurance and discipline are main principals in my every-day life.

CONTACT

Address

Corso San Gottardo 1, 20136 Milano

Telephone

+491703239259

Fmail

nataliewischkowski@web.de

Linkedin

@natalie-wisckkowsk

EDUCATION & TRAINING

Jan 2018 - Present First Level Master Course in

Fashion Direction: Communication and

Brand Management

Politecnico di Milano, Bocconi University, Catholic University of Sacro Cuore,

Milan, Italy

Sep 2013 - Dec 2017 Bachelor of Arts (BA) in

Business Administration (Grade: 1.7)

Fachhochschule Würzburg - Schweinfurt

University of Applied Sciences

Würzburg - Germany

Sep 2014 - Jan 2015 Semester Abroad

Konkuk University Seoul - South Korea

LINGUISTIC COMPETENCES

Mother Tongue German & Polish

Other languages English, French, Italian & Korean

Language qualification Korean & Italian language Certificate

Self-Evaluation (European Level)

	Comprehension		Speaking		Writing
	Listening	Reading	Spoken interaction	Linguistic production	
English	C 1	C 1	C 1	C 1	C 1
French	A 2	A 2	A 2	A 2	A 2
Italian	A 2	A 2	A 2	A 2	A 2
Korean	A 1	A 1	A 1	A 1	A 1

Natalie Wischkowski

Curriculum Vitae



PROFILE

I am passionate about fashion, interested in different cultures and strive to overcome challenges. Based on my experience as a former competitive athlete in fencing, self-reliance, endurance and discipline are main principals in my every-day life.

CONTACT

Address

Corso San Gottardo 1, 20136 Milano

Telephone

+491703239259

Fmail

nataliewischkowski@web.de

Linkedin

@natalie-wisckkowski

SOCIAL & ORGANIZATIONAL COMPETENCES

- Project Management
- International Experience
- Motivation and Commitment
- Communication

- Teamwork
- Flexibility
- Discipline
- Intercultural Experience

INFORMATIC COMPETENCES

- Microsoft Office Windows® / Apple® OS X
 (Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Access, Outlook)
- Adobe® suite (InDesign, Photoshop)

INTERESTS

- Fashion
- Global Economy
- Travel

- Foreign cultures and languages
- Fencing & Crossfit

Milan, 27 August 2018

